redspottedhanky.com 2012-06-06

# Privacy Policy & Data Protection Policy - redspottedhanky.com

This privacy policy outlines the procedures redspottedhanky.com has in place regarding the collection and use of any personal information (i.e. information from which you can be identified) that you give to us, or that we collect when you use this website or SMS feedback service. We respect your privacy and take care in the storage and use of your personal information. 

## Privacy & Data Protection Policy

This privacy policy sets out how we collect and use personal and other data that you provide to us when you use our web site & related booking service (“our Services”).

We respect your privacy and so we collect and process all data in accordance with UK data protection legislation currently in force.

This policy is effective from 23rd June 2010 but may be changed from time to time by updates to this page. Please review this policy on a regular basis to ensure that you are happy with it.

If you have any questions on our policy [please email us.](mailto:atosonline@atosorigin.com)

## Data that we will collect

In order to use our Services we need to collect certain data about you. In addition we prefer to collect some data about you for the purposes set out in the section headed ‘use of your data’ below. Some of the data that we collect will be personal data in that it will be capable of identifying you. For instance your name and address. When you register to use our services you will be given the option to opt out of some of the data collection activities that we do.

When you use our service we will collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

  * Data that you provide to us when you register for use of the site or our Services
  * Data that you provide when you use any of the services that we provide
  * Data about your computer such as your IP address and use of our site (eg. Frequency & length of visits, pages visited)

## Use of your data

We will use personal data that we collect in the following ways:

  * To provide and administer the Services to you
  * To administer our loyalty card scheme
  * To operate the site from a technical and practical perspective
  * For internal record keeping
  * To personalise your use of the site (for instance, to follow up on purchases made on the site)
  * For the purposes of customer care (for instance, responding to complaints)

In addition to the use of your information as we have described above we may (if you have specifically opted in on registration with us) use your personal data to send you emails and marketing communications from us and from third parties.

Our use of your data for the above purposes may require us to pass on the information to third parties.

## Overseas transfers of data 

Information that we collect from you may be processed by us in any country in which we operate or by third parties in any country. Some of those countries (for instance the United States) do not have data protection laws in place that are equivalent to those in the UK and your rights in those countries may not be as strong. You expressly consent to those transfers.

## ‘Cookies' and internet tags

A cookie is a file that is stored on your computer that allows our website to recognise that your computer has accessed our site previously. We use cookies to collect and process anonymous information about your visit to our website such as, which pages you visited, how long you spent on those pages, how often you visit. We will use this information to improve the contents of our site or to collate statistics about it, or to otherwise improve and personalise our services to you. You can set your computer to refuse to accept cookies and to delete current cookies held on your computer but this will be likely to have a negative effect on your use of our website (for instance because the website will no longer recognise your computer). You can get more information about cookies from www.allaboutcookies.org.

We may also use Internet tags in combination with cookies on this website, and may deploy these tags through a third-party advertising partner. We use this technology to help us analyse the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns. The third-party partner may be able to collect anonymous aggregated data about visitors to other sites, because of these Internet tags and cookies.

## Security 

Transactions over the internet are not in themselves secure so we cannot guarantee the security of the personal data that you provide to us. We will however take reasonable technical and organisational measures to prevent the loss or corruption of your data in accordance with UK data protection legislation.

## Third Party Websites.

Our web site contains links to third party web sites through which you may book other services (for example event ticketing & European rail tickets). Once you operate the link you have left our web site and we are not in control of those websites or the use of personal data that you provide when you use their services. Please ensure that you are happy with the privacy policy which is applicable to the relevant website.

## Your rights 

If you are unhappy with our policy you may at any time amend the permissions that you have given in relation to use of your data by accessing your account on the website or by clicking the unsubscribe link in any emails that we send you

You may also ask us to provide details of the personal information that we hold about you by [emailing us.](mailto:atosonline@atosorigin.com)

We may charge a fee for providing this information.

If you think any information we have about you is incorrect or incomplete, [please email us as soon as possible.](mailto:atosonline@atosorigin.com)

## Cookie Policy

We use cookies to collect and process anonymous information about your visit to our website such as, which pages you visited, how long you spent on those pages, how often you visit. We will use this information to improve the contents of our site or to collate statistics about it, or to otherwise improve and personalise our services to you.
